OLIVIA KALINOWSKI

19 Newark Bay Ct., Bayonne, NJ 07002 Ph: 201 424 3985 o.kalinowski27@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Web Developer with a Bachelor's Degree in Journalism/ Media Studies from Rutgers University and work experience in customer service. Skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with a passion for problem solving. Motivated learner, excited to dive into challenging tasks. Strengths include excellent multitasker to meet deadlines, working in a team, and creating projects from start to finish.

Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
 - Adobe Photoshop CS5
- Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel

Experience

Benefits Specialist

March 2019-June 2019

Conduent - Secaucus, NJ

- Handle clients' Health & Welfare Benefits during Annual Enrollment period
- Understand Health & Welfare to educate clients about their available benefits

Sr. Customer Service Representative

Apr 2018 – *March 2019*

Advance Local Customer Care — Secaucus, NJ

- Resolve customer's escalated service complaints
- Review files, records, and other documents to obtain information to respond to requests.
- Compare data with source documents, and re-enter data in verification format to detect errors
- Calculate the weekly budget used for each publication from weekly invoices

English Teacher Oct 2016—Jun 2017

SOCRATES School of Foreign Languages — Warsaw, Poland

- Taught 1st through 4th grades
- Planned daily lessons and activities to actively engage the students
- Adapted teaching methods and instructional materials to meet students' varying needs and interests.

Photography Intern

Jan 2016 – May 2016

Hearst Magazines Studio D - New York City, New York

- Assisted the photographers with lighting/ grip equipment set up and break down on editorial and advertorial shoots
- Assisted all incoming visitors (magazine editors, models, photographers' assistants, etc.) with whatever they needed
- Answered the phones, kept thorough details by logging in/out products for each photo shoot
- Kept the studio organized by resetting each studio set with the proper equipment and tools

Education

Certificate from Rutgers Coding Bootcamp Web Development Program
Bachelor of Arts from Rutgers University — New Brunswick, NJ
Bachelor's Degree in English and Journalism/Media Studies

September 2019 May 2016